One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
A newborn child bears no sin.
Garp.
Take care of my child.
Your father is...
the Pirate King, Gold Roger!
Fire Fist Ace... is Gold Roger's son?!
This is huge news!
Call the main office right away! We're releasing an extra for this!
So, it still lives...
The...
The blood of the Pirate King lives on!
Ace and Whitebeard
So, he isn't Luffy's real brother?
Roger's...
son?
So his biological son lives on? What a miracle.
Anyone who had a connection to Roger back then should have already been executed!
Since he's Luffy-san's brother, I assumed Dragon was his father, too...
I thought so too! What's going on here?
Does this mean they aren't really brothers?
Can you believe this, Garp?
A child's about to be born...
...My child.
Unfortunately, I'll have left this world by the time that happens.
And why are you telling this to me, a marine?
Roger!
The mother of that child, and any woman with ties to you, will undoubtedly be executed!
That's why I'm telling you.
The Government is sure to figure out where I've been this past year.
They'll find her, and then they'll kill her.
But... a newborn child bears no sin.
Garp! You and I have nearly killed each other countless times.
I trust you as much as I would a member of my own crew!
Protect him for me.
Don't try that selfish crap on me!
No, I know you'll do it!
Take care of my child!
And you're sure this is the island?
Roger was spotted here, but he was behaving differently.
He was acting almost like a father.
Roger's era is over.
We must eradicate all traces of his bloodline.
Investigate every child born during the ten months following his imprisonment.
Investigate all pregnant women, as well.
Kill any mother who seems suspicious.
Five children were born this month.
The following are expected to give birth next month...
Not yet.
You can't be born yet.
I'm sorry.
Not yet.
Not yet... Not yet...
If you're a girl, your name will be Ann.
If you're a boy, it'll be Ace.
Those are the names he chose.
Our child's name is Gol D. Ace.
This is our child.
Rouge!
Rouge! Hang in there!
You take care of him, Dadan!
No way...!
Whose kid is that?
Dadan?
That's right. From now on, this is where you'll be living.
Huh?
You're going to be living with these guys. Try to get along with them.
As annoying as it is,
both me and Luffy carry the blood of a world-renowned criminal.
Even though I owe my mother a debt of gratitude and took the name "Portgas"...
I still can't stand the thought that I carry the blood of that worthless father of mine.
Gramps...
My old man is...
Whitebeard. And no one else.
Garp...
It's been two years now, hasn't it?
Since you took the name of your mother, formed the Spade Pirates,
and ventured to the seas with formidable strength and speed.
At that point, we finally realized...
...that we had not stopped Roger's bloodline!
But Whitebeard, who realized this truth at the same time as us,
decided to raise you to become the next Pirate King,
and let the son of his former rival on to his own ship!
That's not true!
I got on that ship so I could make the old man the Pirate King!
You're the only one who thinks that!
We were careful not to act recklessly...
You were under Whitebeard's protection!
But left unchecked, you'd undoubtedly inspire a new generation of pirates.
That is why your execution here today carries such great significance.
Even if we must go to war against Whitebeard!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
Reporting in!
The Gates of Justice are opening, but nobody's ordered them to!
We can't get in touch with the control room, either!
What?!
They opened!
What's going on here?!
The Gates of Justice are opening on their own!
Didn't the Navy say they wouldn't open it for us?
The control room is most likely inside Marineford. Who could have done this?
Here it comes! It is time!
C-Captain Buggy, it can't be...!
The time has come!
Don't tell me, you're...!
I never realized you were actually God's messenger!
Seriously?! Buggy!
Of course it's not true! There must be some sort of trick here!
He's right... Who the hell opened the Gate?!
No...! Could Heaven itself want to make me the Pirate King?!
They're here!
All troops, prepare for battle!
They appeared so suddenly! But where did they come from?!
It's a huge fleet of pirate ships!
Where is Whitebeard? Find him!
"Bohemian Knight" Doma!
"Thunder Lord" McGuy!
The DeCalvan Brothers!
"Whirl Spider" Squard!
Every one of these mighty figures... They're all captains renowned throughout the New World!
There are forty-three ships in total.
Whitebeard and his commanders are nowhere to be found.
But these pirates are definitely allied with Whitebeard!
Can you see Ace-chan?
There he is! Ace!
Don't get thrown off by this! You're all hopeless!
You guys...?
Shall we attack them?
No, wait. Whitebeard's must be around here somewhere!
He's waiting for the right moment. Watch the water!
Now it's getting interesting! I'm really getting excited here!
Hurry and show up, Whitebeard!
It can't be!
Where is he coming from?
Well, he sure picked one amazing place to show up.
We never considered this!
There's a shadow beneath the surface!
No way!
So that's how they did it?
They coated their entire fleet and came here along the bottom of the sea!
It's the Moby Dick!
Three more of Whitebeard's ships have appeared!
They've broken into the bay!
T-That's...
The commander of the First Division, Marco!
All 14 commanders are here!
How long has it been, Sengoku?
Whitebeard!
I take it my beloved son...
is still doing well?
How could you get in here so easily...?!
Vwe've made it past the gates!
Now then, Vi wonder if vyou and Ace-boy's father will show up.
Ace's father?
Since his son Ace is about to be executed, Vi'm sure Dragon will do something!
Oh, me and Ace don't have the same dad.
My dad is Dragon...
but Ace's dad is Gold Roger.
What?!
I never got to meet him, but I hear he's pretty amazing.
But Ace gets mad whenever I say that.
What?!
Oh, yeah. That's supposed to be a secret.
Wait just a little longer, Ace.
Old man!
W-What?
A crack... in the air?!
What kind of blast is that?!
Not good! Look at the size of that wave!
A seaquake?! He can make even the oceans shake?!
There's one on the other side, too!
Is this Whitebeard's power?!
I'm going on ahead!
Take care, Ace!
Sure! So long, Luffy!
Yeah! When I set out to sea in three years, I'll have gotten even stronger!
Yeah!
Ace!
Now, let's go cause some trouble!
That kid...! He went and became a pirate?!
A pirate ship! It's a flag I've never seen before!
This is a pirate who's been growing in strength recently.
D...? Where is he from?
We don't know yet, but he's a rookie who wields the power of a Logia Devil Fruit!
A kid with some strength has shown up in the Grand Line!
It seems he turned down an offer to join the Seven Warlords.
How old are these kids?
Why do the young ones always have to be in such a hurry?
Are you serious, Captain?!
I want to meet him, no matter what!
Red-Haired Shanks!
The Spade Pirates?
The famous Super Rookies... have come for me?
No, that's not what I'm here for!
You saved my little brother's life. He always talks about you.
I just wanted to thank you in person.
You mean Luffy?!
I never knew he had a brother!
I see. I'm glad you came!
Please, tell me more!
Let's have a party!
Hey, big guy! I wanna meet this Whitebeard!
I'm not going to allow a kid with murderous intent to see the old man!
Captain! That's Jinbe!
Really? One of the Seven Warlords?
Well, that's gonna be a problem.
I may not be a member of the Whitebeard Pirates...
but I feel it is my duty to face you!
It's been five days, and they're still fighting!
They might both die at this rate!
Ace!
What's that?!
Where's the kid who wants to take my head?
As you wish, I'll take you on!
It's the Whitebeard Pirates!
I'll take care of this myself.
You guys!
Captain! Captain Ace, what are you doing?!
Run, you guys!
Captain!
What? You're gonna run away now?
I'm letting my crew escape.
I'm staying in their place. I won't run!
What a cheeky little brat you are!
I'm...
You still tryin' to stand up?
I'd hate to see you die here, kid.
If you still want to fight,
then take my name and roam the seas wild and free!
Become my son!
You've gotta be kidding me!
I'm the commander of the Fourth Division... Thatch!
Since you're joining our crew,
I think we should be friends.
Shut up!
You sure woke up in a bad mood.
Oh, yeah. Do you want to know what happened after you passed out?
Your companions came to get you back... so we beat them all.
What? It's not like they're dead.
We're keeping them here on this ship.
Are you sure you should leave me like this, without any locks or shackles or anything?
Shackles? We don't need those!
Hey, hey, what d'ya think your doing?
You should be more considerate at this time of night!
Hey, he fell overboard!
And he can't swim, either!
Someone, go save him!
He does this every day. He has real persistence.
Was that the hundredth time?
I think so.
You guys...
Why do you call him your father, anyway?
Because he calls us his sons.
To the rest of the world we're all just outcasts.
It makes us happy.
It's just a word, but it makes us happy!
Hey, how long are you gonna keep risking your life like this?
Make up your mind already!
You won't be able to take pops' head in your current condition.
Are you gonna get off this ship and start over...
or are you gonna stay here...
and take on Whitebeard's mark?
You're Doma, right?
Wow! Ace did it again!
He made Doma's crew surrender, all on his own!
Me, become the Second Division Commander?
We've haven't had one for a long time.
Everybody would definitely accept you!
You've been here a lot longer than I have, right? Are you sure it's okay?
It's fine, don't worry about it.
I don't have that kind of ambition anyway.
Go ahead, Commander Ace!
Really? What a surprise!
So, that's how it is?
You don't really act like Roger, though...
Wasn't he your enemy?
Aren't you gonna throw me out?
When you said you had something
important to talk about, I thought it would be more important than this...
It doesn't matter who your parents were. Everyone is a child of the sea.
It looks like another incredible man has joined Whitebeard's crew.
They say he's unbelievably strong!
Stop it, Ace! Calm down!
The old man said he'd make an exception, just this once!
You don't have to chase after Teach!
Let me go! He was a member of my division!
If I just ignore this, Thatch won't be able to rest in peace!
Ace.
It's fine, just this once.
I have a weird feeling about this.
He killed a crewmate and escaped!
After living under your protection for so many years...
he just spat right in your face!
Above all else, he tarnished his father's name.
Do you think I can just ignore that?
I'll settle this!
Hey, wait! Come back, Ace!
Ace!
Old man...
All of you...
I ignored your orders and ran off! Why didn't you just abandon me?!
This only happened because I was so stubborn!
No...
I was the one who told you to go...
my son.
You're lying! Don't be ridiculous!
You tried to stop me back then, but I...!
I told you to go!
I told him to go. Isn't that right, Marco?
Yeah, I heard it too. We sent you into a lot of trouble, huh, Ace?
This entire ocean should know...
what happens when someone...
harms one of our crewmates.
Anyone who hurts you won't be allowed to live, Ace!
Hang on! We're coming for you, right now!
Prepare yourselves, Navy HQ!
He's gathered quite an impressive group, huh?
What are they going on about?
I've got a bad feeling about this.
What are these tremors?!
Here it comes. The seaquake that he set off earlier...
is coming back as a tsunami!
The earthquake man, who ate the Tremor-Tremor Fruit...
"Whitebeard", Edward Newgate!
What is that?!
It's a tsunami! It's huge!
We might outnumber them, but don't assume that it guarantees our victory...
It's possible that we will be the ones to meet our end!
That man...
has the power to destroy the world!
It's starting...
The war!
Let's go!
Whitebeard and his fleet of fourty-seven pirate ships from the New World are attacking.
Standing against them are the
Government's two greatest forces:
Navy HQ and the
Seven Royal Warlords of the Sea.
No matter who the winner is... no matter who the loser is...
the era will change.